### **Dayoung Kim**

### Front-end developer

Address	Gyeongsan-si, Gyeongsangbuk-do, Republic of Korea
Mobile	+82 10 2869 7886
Email	kimdayoung771 @gmail.com
LinkedIn	https://www.linkedin.c om/in/dayoung-clara- kim/
Github	https://github.com/Day oung3460

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

Junior Front-End Developer experiencing in a company that develops and services a blockchain-based platform. Skilled in developing and testing multiple web-based applications. Gained skills in aligning designs with client requirements and experience in resolving conflicts with colleagues professionally. Specializes in vanilla JavaScript and vue.js framework. Willing to learn native mobile development.

#### **EDUCATION**

programming academy, Deagu, Mar 2020 ~ Sep 2020

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap
- WebSocket
- JavaScript / jQuery
- TypeScript
- AJAX
- Vue.is
- React.js
- Git

#### WORK HISTORY

# Coinvest – Gyeongsan-si, South Korea Front-end developer

: Nov 2020 ~ Present

- Worked with a design team to resolve CSS issues.
- Design pages and components
- Turn design pages and components into vue.js
- Worked with back-end team collaboratively to make API specification

## Cryptocurrency Exchange Website (Jun 2021 ~ Present)

- Managing cryptocurrency exchange website development projects from initial design
- Using vue.js framework, Rest API(axios) and Web Socket
- Received real-time transaction data and drew a graph using Trading View chart library
- Library used:
  - qrcode for OTP login
  - big-js to calculate big decimal
  - vue-i18n for translation

## Jangboda, a traditional market delivery application (Nov 2020 ~ May 2021)

- Developed and maintained webview for hybrid application.
- Using vue.js framework and Rest API(axios)
- Using Kakao map open API
- Using NICE open API for user authentication
- The monthly active users was recorded average 500.